{
    "id": "03a101cb97a24feea947b407df1aeee8",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She devoted her life ………………….. helping the poor and the destitute.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Bad weather didn’t deter us ……………… starting our vacation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Punishment is not necessarily a deterrent ……………….. crime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Be wary ………………… politicians who claim to be devoted public servants.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I despise anyone who is cruel ………………. animals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We were desolated ……………….. the death of our good friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The desire ………………. fame drove him relentlessly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Some animals can survive ...................... very little water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She was deprived …………………. her membership for nonpayment of dues.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I deposited 100 dollars ……………… my savings account.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}